What is all this?
What the hell... happened here?
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Welcome back, Emperor.
Did something happen?
I saw some craters on the asphalt out there.
I was just asking the same thing.
Go on, Kou.
Yes...
Moments ago, I identified two intruders
entering the concealed area
as well as two escapees.
One intruder and one escapee
have been exterminated.
I terminated a man with scouting abilities
and Souma sacrificed himself
through large-scale materialization.
However, I couldn't stop the other intruder
and Hikari Ebina's escape.
Did you trace them?
The large-scale materialization gave
them just enough time to get away.
Their whereabouts are unknown.
It's my fault...
What's your fault?
I mean, none of this would have
happened if it weren't for me.
I didn't even notice they planned this.
I wonder how they were able
to even locate us here.
Raion.
What did you tell Souma
when you brought him here?
I asked him to come with me to the power
station since the power wasn't working.
On the way over, I threatened him,
telling him I was working with the Emperor.
I doubt anyone can resist
after hearing that.
And his absence could be easily explained
with the guise of fixing the power.
In that case, they likely haven't realized
that Raion has changed sides.
See! It's not your fault, Raion!
Y-Yeah...
The Queen has full trust
in Haruto's Negotiation Right.
Still, it's odd that the Materialization
Right hasn't been released,
even though its owner died.
The Immobilization Right's principle fixation!
Hirayama must have fixed
Souma's Materialization Right!
The fixation will stand as long as Hirayama,
Knight, and Lili don't all die.
So that's why Yagihashi
decided to save Lili.
Raion.
That's enough for today.
Let's regroup tomorrow night.
Sometimes the best thing is to wait and see.
Sure, I understand.
What?!
But he just got here! Right?!
Don't say that.
There's no need to fill us in.
People died again because of me...
Maybe I should just stop trying.
Hayato and Sensei gave their lives
because they believed in you!
Stop whining and live up to their faith,
if you consider them your friend!
I've already decided to give my all.
Those two didn't fight
so we could mope around!
Sorry.
You're right, I shouldn't be the one mourning.
Raion-kun, you've done
your part to the fullest.
Whether that'll bear fruit
will depend entirely
on Ebina-kun's information.
I'm here with information
from Hirayama and Iruga.
First off is Seraphiel.
His full name is Gonzaburo Tanonaka.
There's no doubt he's a genuine priest.
Iruga checked at City Hall.
Seraphiel...
Gonzaburo Tanonaka...
As for his Prime Right, all we know is
that it's under the Production Attribute.
And I'm not sure what this refers to, but,
something is supposed to "ignite"
at 21:00 on the day after my escape.
Finally, this is a message from Hirayama.
"We've organized a plan to defeat
Queen Kisaragi... to commence today."
Defeat the Queen?
Is that even possible, like for real?
As long as he works together with Fukami.
So, Hirayama and Fukami.
What is all this fuss about?
Lady Kisaragi...
This man, Yohei Fukami is a traitor!
What do you mean?
Hikari Ebina's escape
was organized by Fukami!
There was something off about
that woman from the start!
That's why I befriended her and
kept her under my surveillance!
I've seen him talking with her many times!
I was wondering what this was about.
You better cut the crap!
Like Fukami says,
his accusation is quite a reach...
I've kept Hirayama on a long leash figuring
he'd expose himself eventually,
but how unfortunate for Fukami
to be used like this.
The Queen has next to zero
trust in Hirayama and me.
We'll use that to build
her trust in Fukami instead.
Lady Kisaragi, you wouldn't mind
if I killed him, would ya?
I suppose not.
If that's what you want, I won't hold back!
Prime Right of Immobilization!
Immobilize his heart!
Wha—?!
My Immobilization Right isn't working?!
I've engaged a counter attack
with my Transfer Right.
If you don't display an intent
to transfer your Prime Right to me,
your attack will rebound back to yourself.
You have a choice between
your Prime Right and your life.
The Transfer Right can do that?
We'll lie about the Transfer Right's
ability so she'll look on as they fight.
Fine, take that!
Transfer!
We've confirmed that the Evasion Right
can't stop the Transfer Right.
So if we can blindside her,
that should finish the job.
Hang on, Hikari.
Are you saying that...
Fukami killing Rika was part
of your plan all along?
We needed to do whatever we could
to gain her trust and let her guard down.
I'm sorry.
But it helped to create
an opening to the Queen.
If we can just time it right, she won't
be able to stop the Transfer Right.
No, I don't think it'll be that easy.
You may be able to kill the Queen.
However... your plan will fail.
I expected this to happen anyway.
As long as the Queen's dead,
that's all that matters!
I've finally settled things.
Fukami, ready for the final blow?!
Let's do it!
I command Kou Kirishima's heart to...
Send my injuries to Kou...
Immobilize!
Transfer!
It's no use.
We've prepared in case things came to this.
Prime Right of Resurrection.
How careless of me...
I didn't see that coming.
Your clothing...
Allow me to change it back
with the Recurrence Right.
That can't be...
So that's how!
Fail?! What are you talking about?!
It's very simple.
The Queen doesn't own the powers.
The owner is her deputy officer, Kou.
How did I fail to notice...
It was you all along... Kou...
D-Damn it!
The time has come...
It's time to tell you all the truth,
now that the stars have aligned.
Sudo-kun and I are working
together with Iruga-kun.
We'll explain from the very beginning.
Stay calm and listen carefully.
The Queen's ultimate goal
is to find Teppei Yoshii
and seize the Obedience Right.
Teppei Yoshii... Isn't he the guy who's...
Iruga's best friend and owner
of the Obedience Right.
He's the one who died during the test run.
One month ago...
After we declared the end of Tasuketsu,
Ren Iruga returned to the Camp.
There, he happened to see Maria Kisaragi.
This is before she first
appeared as the Queen.
Why would she go to the Camp?
And how did she even know
about it in the first place?
Apparently, the Queen was looking over some
documents about the Emperor and Teppei-kun.
That's how she found out about
Teppei Yoshii's Obedience Right?
But why was she researching those two?
That's because...
the three of them are blood siblings.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
It wasn't just the Emperor and the Queen?
Teppei Yoshii was related too?!
As I explained before,
they're relatives of mine.
Not that we were ever very close.
One day, their parents passed away
in a car accident.
The three of them were each
adopted by a different family.
The eldest daughter, Maria,
by the Kisaragis in Saitama,
the first-born son, Teppei,
by the Yoshiis in Okayama,
and the second-born son, Haruto,
by the Yanagis in Saitama.
We were such distant relatives,
all the arrangements had been made
by the time we found out what happened.
No wonder they all have
different last names.
Maria Kisaragi always had
a strong love for her family,
but I imagine it's only grown stronger
with the death of her parents
and being separated from her siblings.
You see, she wants them all back.
Her family... and everything she loves.
That explains the Queen's full trust
in the Negotiation Right.
As long as the Emperor says so,
she believes it's foolproof.
She won't second guess the Emperor
because she loves him as her little brother.
Just like Kazuki always
believed in me, no matter what...
That doesn't make any of what
they did okay. But still...
That Tasuketsu the other day...
You're a male with the blood type RH-O
who has lived in Niimi City, Okayama Prefecture.
The male with the blood type RH-O
who lived in Niimi, Okayama...
It was about Teppei Yoshii.
Hang on, that question was meant
to keep Teppei alive, which means...
The Queen doesn't know that he's dead.
And as one of the casualties
from the test run,
Teppei Yoshii's body should be
a part of the tower.
What?! Is that how that tower
was made, for real?!
If the Queen's side were ever
to figure that out,
naturally, she'll turn the tower back
into a pile of bodies and revive him.
The Resurrection Right was for
in case Teppei had died?
Her vision is to revive and reunite with her
siblings in a church with the priest's blessing.
That's why she selected their base as
that church, together with Seraphiel.
Blessing? What does that
have to do with anything?
It means everything to her.
She's reuniting with her siblings, after all.
Everything clicked when I learned
that Seraphiel is a real priest.
So how do you know Kou owns the powers?
There's no definitive proof.
But based on the information we've
gathered, it's the only viable option.
We assumed so by the time
we helped Knight escape,
which is why we separated Kou from the Queen.
As a result, the Queen couldn't stop
so much as the Suspension Right.
Of her first servants, the only one
who's survived this entire time
is Kou of the Three Powers.
It's not the Queen who holds the powers
with Kou being the brains.
Rather, it's most likely the opposite.
Besides, the main culprit and
fundamental source is the itako
who brought the Rights into this world.
Saneatsu Narita's Medical Records
The Camp already existed
One Kidney Lost in Accident
when Narita-kun was handed
the Parental Authority eleven years ago.
At the time, Maria Kisaragi was just thirteen.
The Emperor was only a baby.
Not to mention, their parents were
healthy and she lived a normal life.
In other words, it makes no sense
for her to be the itako.
The itako is Kou of the Three Powers!
So what are we supposed to do now?
Don't you see? We have
two ultimate trump cards.
Trump cards?
The first is Ren Iruga.
He'll inform the Queen of Teppei Yoshii's
death and lead her to the final stage.
That's the "ignition."
Since we've already gathered all the facts,
we can predict the Queen's moves
and strategize for battle.
What's the second one?
I suspect you already know.
Now allow me to share the details of our plan.
Remember your roles as I just explained.
Ignition is set for tomorrow at 21:00.
I'll be off now,
to start "prepping."
We've connected all the dots.
Iruga and Teppei both escaped during
the Camp's major breach three years ago.
Teppei ran to Kanagawa in search
of independence, and Iruga eventually
entered our school after being taken
in by Gunjosora Orphanage in Tokyo.
That's where he met Yagihashi, who
he'd heard about from Teppei.
And...
Iruga-kun had stolen one
envelope from the Camp.
He gave it to me knowing I was
Teppei-kun's cousin, just in case.
What?! So you were working
with Iruga before Tasuketsu?
No, that wasn't until after
we defeated the Emperor.
When I heard about the Emperor
from Mido, I thought of Haruto-kun.
Given my knowledge that Teppei-kun
and Haruto-kun were siblings,
I figured Iruga-kun would eventually
visit the Emperor's tower.
To see the remains
of Teppei's little brother...
That's where I spoke with Iruga-kun
and learned of Maria Kisaragi's actions.
That led me to form this final plan:
for the Queen to revive Teppei-kun.
Hence the ignition.
What?! But...
Isn't it risky to let them
resurrect him on the spot?
Like I mentioned,
she's the type of person to go out of
her way to select a church as her base.
She even has her priest
friend accompany her.
Her attachment to family and
the church are very much real.
You mean she'll take him back
to the church to revive him?
As far as I know, that would be her instinct.
That's why this plan will...
Iruga, what did you just say?!
Hmm? Honestly, I'm a bit surprised
to see you so surprised!
To repeat what I said...
Could the person you're searching
for be Teppei Yoshii by any chance?
How do you know Teppei?
Well you see, Teppei-chan was
my best friend back at the Camp.
Best friend?
You're a male with the blood type RH-O
who has lived in Niimi City, Okayama Prefecture.
That question from the other day
fit his description and...
The Emperor looks a bit
like Teppei-chan, too.
Then what was his personality like?
He has a strong sense of justice, he's honest,
but also kinda ditsy and a bit nosy!
You really do know him...
Not only that,
I know where Teppei-chan is.
I-Is that true, Iruga?!
Of course it is. I would never lie
to my best friend's siblings!
Tell me! Where is he?!
That's for you to find out tomorrow
night, when Raion-kun comes.
Seeing as he's the Emperor's
best friend and all.
Wouldn't you wanna share
that precious moment?
Yeah! I wanna wait to find out with Raion!
I'm best friends with Teppei-chan, who's
siblings with the Queen and Emperor.
And somehow, we were all
able to meet each other!
It's gotta be either fate or a miracle!
We even have this church
as the perfect venue!
I bet Teppei-chan will be
glad to reunite here!
You're right. We will reunite,
here in this church, with His blessing!
A blue sky... white clouds...
Boo!
Jeez Knight, don't scare me like that.
I scared Raion!
He has zero sense of urgency.
This is our only chance to relax.
To be honest, I didn't trust you... Sorry.
It can't be helped.
I don't deny that I was being suspicious.
And I didn't want any information getting out.
You're a difficult dude to deal with.
Why do you think the Queen went
to the Camp in the first place?
Everything began with the itako
sealing the Rights into envelopes.
That itako being Kou Kirishima. I suspect he
was a key person in the Camp's establishment.
The chief culprit...
The Queen visited the Camp
because she was tipped off by Kou.
That's the most reasonable explanation.
The Emperor didn't seem to know about Kou.
I bet the Queen couldn't
bring herself to admit
she worked with one of the Camp's founders.
The ignition is happening tonight, right?
That's right, and that's the sign
to commence our final plan.
Which is a ridiculous plan, by the way.
You guys are crazy.
You think so? I think it's appropriate.
It's crazy, but awesome.
So I'll risk my life for it!
You and Gobo-kun are our key players.
We're counting on you.
Yeah, let's make it happen!
The Emperor is playing with Kai.
I'll engage my Prime Right of Isolation.
I've isolated this room
from the outside world.
This blocks any exchanges between the two.
Is this how you defended against Hirayama-kun
and Fukami-kun's attacks yesterday?
Kisaragi-san, you died, right?
What did it feel like?
I wish you wouldn't ask me
such a vulgar question.
I apologize for yesterday.
My late response caused you pain.
Please, that was nothing.
We're indebted to your powers anyways.
But regardless, who knew...
The Queen as the brains with no powers
and Kou-kun as the true ruler.
This set up worked surprisingly well!
What's the status of
Hirayama and Fukami's Rights?
Still no good.
All released Rights are supposed
to be returned, but...
But they didn't come back.
It has to be the Immobilization Right.
It's still in place even after their deaths.
Oh well. The Transfer Right is a big loss,
but we'll have to make do.
Why don't you have Kou-kun gift you
a Prime Right as well, Kisaragi-san?
It's not like it would cost you any sacrifices.
I'm fine. I don't like
doing things I'm not used to.
Besides, everything will be over soon.
After Iruga tells me where Teppei
is tonight, we'll be reunited.
My wish will come true.
Is that so... what a shame.
We can use the Rights however
we wish as long as we have "it,"
Kou-kun's greatest invention of the century:
The ultra space-time construction
interference device.
Either Fate, or a Miracle
The Mother Light...